const List<Map<String, dynamic>> definitionsSetUpExercise = [
  {
    "exercise_id": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "game_key": 4,
    "description": "Type past participles"
  },
];

const List<Map<String, dynamic>> definitionsSetUpQuestions = [
  {
    'question': 'a state or condition markedly different from the norm',
    'answer': 'abjure,0,evanescent,0,aberration,1,intimation,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 1,
  },
  {
    'question': 'abusive language used to express blame or censure',
    'answer': 'ostensible,0,dirge,0,clamor,0,invective,1',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'transparently clear; easily understandable',
    'answer': 'vitriolic,0,pellucid,1,impinge,0,equivocal,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 3,
  },
  {
    'question': 'something causing misery or death',
    'answer': 'bane,1,adamant,0,wanton,0,pernicious,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 4,
  },
  {
    'question': 'conspicuously and outrageously bad or reprehensible',
    'answer': 'emend,0,egregious,1,expunge,0,onerous,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 5,
  },
  {
    'question': 'generally incompetent and ineffectual',
    'answer': 'abjure,0,evanescent,0,confidant,0,inept,1',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 6,
  },
  {
    'question': 'exultantly proud and joyful; in high spirits',
    'answer': 'elated,1,deferential,0,insular,0,avarice,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 7,
  },
  {
    'question': 'able to work as intended or able to succeed',
    'answer': 'amiable,0,diligent,0,viable,1,intrepid,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 8,
  },
  {
    'question': 'showing disapproval',
    'answer': 'vicissitude,0,pejorative,1,multifarious,0,alacrity,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 9,
  },
  {
    'question': 'interpret or assign meaning',
    'answer': 'construe,1,alacrity,0,incumbent,0,travesty,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 10,
  },
  {
    'question': 'instructive with a moral intent',
    'answer': 'convivial,0,largess,0,didactic,1,solipsism,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 11,
  },
  {
    'question': 'showing a strong desire for attention, approval, or publicity',
    'answer': 'thirstry,1,zoodle,0,droning,0,deepfake,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 12,
  },
  {
    'question': 'angry; irritated',
    'answer': 'abjure,0,broigus,1,awfy,0,puggle,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 13,
  },
  {
    'question': 'without qualification',
    'answer': 'steep,0,perish,0,utter,1,intimation,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 14,
  },
  {
    'question': 'proceed, get along, or succeed',
    'answer': 'fare,1,cede,0,ordain,1,elude,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 15,
  },
  {
    'question': 'not arrogant or presuming',
    'answer':'halting,0,ranging,0,enduring,0,retiring,1',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 16,
  },
  {
    'question': 'work hard to come to terms with or deal with something',
    'answer': 'beguile,0,grapple,1,gentry,0,assiduous,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 17,
  },
  {
    'question': 'diffusing warmth and friendliness',
    'answer': 'interminable,0,veritable,0,affable,1,formidable,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 18,
  },
  {
    'question': 'corrupt morally or by intemperance or sensuality',
    'answer': 'debase,1,thrall,0,rapt,0,wry,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 19,
  },
  {
    'question': 'someone who rebels and becomes an outlaw',
    'answer': 'recourse,0,aide,0,renegade,1,iconoclast,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 20,
  },
  {
    'question': 'artificially formal or stiff',
    'answer': 'roseate,0,tutelage,0,aberration,0,stilted,1',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 21,
  },
  {
    'question': 'lacking tact, shrewdness, or prudence',
    'answer': 'impolitic,1,evanescent,0,indite,0,acme,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 22,
  },
  {
    'question': 'a large number or amount or extent',
    'answer': 'proclivity,0,spate,1,quagmire,0,lode,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 23,
  },
  {
    'question': 'easily excused or forgiven',
    'answer': 'wraith,0,pithy,0,venial,1,hummock,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 24,
  },
  {
    'question': 'cheap showy jewelry or ornament',
    'answer': 'debacle,0,bauble,1,palatial,0,gawk,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 25,
  },
  {
    'question': 'a person who argues to defend some policy or institution',
    'answer': 'apologist,1,gist,0,pucker,0,pert,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 26,
  },
  {
    'question': 'bring or combine together or with something else',
    'answer': 'dissemble,0,divulge,0,amalgamate,1,palatable,0',
    "exercise_key": "Game_4_ex_1",
    "question_id": 27,
  }
];